Inventory of the Richard Wirthlin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Files, 1967-2005 (Box 205-250)
  - Nicolas Lehman interview, 24 September 1998 (Box 240)
  - American Petroleum Institution, 10 November 1998 (Box 240)
  - Western Governors' conference, 17 November 1998 (Box 240)
  - Transport Association, 11 December 1998 (Box 240)
  - Suzanne Smith interview, 1 February 1999 (Box 240)
  - Jack Nelson interview, 10 February 1999 (Box 240)
  - Asia trip, 1 June 1999 (Box 240)
  - APEC speech, 28 June 1999 (Box 240)
  - Peter Robinson interview, 15 July 1999 (Box 240)
  - Bohemian Grove, 22-24 July 1999 (Box 240)
  - California campaign, 30 September 1999 (Box 240)
  - Retreat presentation, 6 April 2001 (Box 240)
  - Friedman Foundation presentation, 18 December 2001 (Box 240)
  - Social and Consumer Trends presentation, 25 February 2002 (Box 240)
  - Post-Olympic LDS church presentation, 1 March 2002 (Box 240)
  - Reagan Coalition, 5 April 2002 (Box 240)
  - Heritage Foundation, 5 April 2002 (Box 240-241)
  - Arizona trip, 11-12 April 2002 (Box 241)
  - Sons of Utah Pioneers, 9 September 2002 (Box 241)
  - Kaile Silva/Peter Pahnke Sealing Salt Lake Temple, 10 September 2005 (Box 241)
  - General Election report, circa 1987 (Box 241)
  - United Kingdom tour file, 1 May 1990 (Box 241)
  - Conservative Party conference report, Oct 1990, 9 October 1990 (Box 241)
  - The Opening of Parliament 1990 report, circa October 1990 (Box 241)
  - Draft of Table of Contents for "War Book,", 6 April 1992 (Box 241)
  - Sir Thomas Arnold, March-July 1993 (Box 241)
  - United Kingdom, circa 1989-1990 (Box 241)
    - Speech pulse, Neil Kinnock, circa Sept 1990 (Box 241)
    - Conservative Party speech pulse, circa 1990 (Box 241)
    - Values, 28 February 1991 (Box 241)
    - Victims of crime memo, 7 September 1990 (Box 241)
    - Scotland, circa April 1990 (Box 241)
    - Speech line, 1 December 1989 (Box 241)
    - Summer values, April-Oct 1990 (Box 241)
  - Reagan 1984 acceptance speech, June-Aug 1984 (Box 241)
  - Presidential debate memos, 1 October 1984 (Box 241)
  - Opposition research, Feb-March 1984 (Box 241)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1980 (Box 241)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1980 (Box 241)
  - Computer turnout, August 29 1980 (Box 241)
  - Articles, clippings, letters, statements, circa 1980 (Box 241)
  - Commitment, August-October 1980 (Box 241)
  - Interview of Pat Caddell and Dick Wirthlin, December 2 1980 (Box 241)
  - Broder, circa 1979 (Box 242)
  - Broder articles, clippings, circa 1980 (Box 242)
  - Dave Broder, circa 1979 (Box 242)
  - Reagan job rating, 1982-1983 (Box 242)
  - Meeting with Frank Fahrenkopf, December 11 1985 (Box 242)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1986 (Box 242)
  - March National transparencies, 1983-1985 (Box 242)
  - Meeting with the President, June 14 1985 (Box 242)
  - Transparencies, March 17 1983 (Box 242)
  - Transparencies of PM, Spring 1984 (Box 242)
  - DMI Business Plan, May 9 1980 (Box 242)
  - Correspondence, September-December 1980 (Box 242)
  - RNCT-1 Transparencies, circa 1980 (Box 242)
  - RNCT-2 Transparencies, 1983-1985 (Box 242)
  - Reagan's Job Rating Transparencies, 1983-1985 (Box 242)
  - White House Memoranda, November 7-10 1983 (Box 242)
  - Presidential debates, circa 1984 (Box 242)
  - Transparencies, circa 1980-1984 (Box 242-243)
    - RNC National VII, September 3-8 1984 (Box 242)
    - Reagan-Bush IV, 1982-1984 (Box 242)
    - National, Februrary-March 1984 (Box 243)
    - National RNC Transparencies, 30615 (Box 243)
    - Perceptual Mapping, circa 1980 (Box 243)
    - National # 13, 30317 (Box 243)
    - Overview document, circa 1980 (Box 243)
  - Richard Richards, circa 1982 (Box 243)
  - Articles, clippings, notes, correspondence, circa 1987 (Box 243)
  - Paul Laxalt, 1987-1988 (Box 243)
    - Strategy, July, 1987 (Box 243)
    - Clippings file, 1987-1988 (Box 243)
    - Articles, correspondence, statements, 1987-1988 (Box 243)
    - Trip, July 28 1987 (Box 243)
    - Correspondence, articles, July, 1987 (Box 243)
    - Meeting, March 23 1987 (Box 243)
    - Laxalt for President materials, circa 1988 (Box 243)
    - July Survey, July, 1985 (Box 243)
    - Notes, correspondence, July, 1987 (Box 243)
    - Survey of adult americans for Senator Paul Laxalt, June 16-18 1987 (Box 243)
    - Executive interviews prepared for Senator Paul Laxalt, 13 August 1985 (Box 243)
  - Nevada Brushfire, August, 1985 (Box 243)
  - White House Memoranda, Aug 5-Sept 2, 1983 (Box 243)
  - White House Memoranda, December 8-20, 1983 (Box 243)
  - Notes and memoranda, February, 1982 (Box 244)
  - Correspondence, Larry Speaks, 1992, 1987 (Box 244)
  - Roger Porter, circa 1986 (Box 244)
  - Mitt Romney meeting, 1990s (Box 244)
  - Ed Rollins, circa 1994 (Box 244)
  - George Romney meeting, March 6, 1992 (Box 244)
  - Advertising Campaign: "Life what a Beautiful Choice," November, 1993 (Box 244)
  - CBS News/New York Times National Survey, circa 1980 (Box 244)
  - New York Times Surveys of the 1980 Election, circa 1980 (Box 244)
  - Camp David meeting, February 5 1982 (Box 244)
  - "The DeMoss Foundation National Attitude Benchmark," Volume 1 of 2, July 1990 (Box 244)
  - "The DeMoss Foundation Youth VISTA," August, 1994 (2 folders) (Box 244)
  - Results of benchmark advertising monitor survey, January, 1992 (Box 244)
  - STRATA analysis, September, 1992 (Box 244)
  - Strategy development "The Virtue of Virtue," October 5 1994 (Box 244)
  - "American Values and Issues Determining Position on Abortion," July, 1990 (Box 244)
  - Project Reed, May 31 2002 (Box 244)
  - Background Research: "The Virtues of Virtue,", March 1 1994 (Box 244)
  - Overview: "Life what a Beautiful Choice," May, 1995 (Box 244)
  - DeMoss STRATA Ads, February, 1993 (Box 244)
  - Notes and memoranda, February 1982 (Box 245)
  - Map of Jerusalem, 1988 (Box 245)
  - Dailey & Associates, circa 1980-1981 (Box 245)
  - Reagan Campaign advertising, circa 1980 (Box 245)
  - Abortion, 1978-1980 (Box 245)
  - Economy, circa 1980 (Box 245)
  - Economic policy memo, 1 April 1980 (Box 245)
  - Reagan and Bush campaign memoranda, 16 Sep-22 Oct 1980 (Box 245)
  - 1984 Bush media campaign, circa 1984 (Box 245)
  - Media-Tuesday team miscellaneous, circa 1984 (Box 245)
  - National tracking survey for the RNC, November-December 1981 (Box 245)
  - Bush 1984 campaign surveys, March-April 1988 (Box 245)
  - California tracking for Bush/Quayle, 1 October 1988 (Box 245)
  - George Bush file, 1978-1988 (Box 245)
  - Key documents, 8 December 1982 (Box 245)
  - Gerrit Gong file, June-October 1984 (Box 245)
  - National-RNC VIII, 1 August 1984 (Box 245)
  - National-RNC IX, 1 September 1984 (Box 245)
  - Campaign memos, 1-30 August 1984 (2 folders) (Box 245)
  - Reagan/Mondale values maps, August-November 1984 (Box 245)
  - Michigan presidential tracking, 9 October 1980 (Box 246)
  - Wyoming statewide study, 25-30 September 1980 (Box 246)
  - Wisconsin statewide data, 16-20 September 1980 (Box 246)
  - Michigan statewide data, 6-15 September 1980 (Box 246)
  - Pennsylvania presidential tracking data, 7 October 1980 (Box 246)
  - Michigan presidential study wave II data, 26-29 September 1980 (Box 246)
  - Pennsylvania tracking data, October 1980 (Box 246)
  - Ohio presidential tracking, 18 October 1980 (Box 246)
  - Ohio presidential tracking data, October 1980 (Box 246)
  - Michigan presidential wave II data, 1 September 1980 (Box 246)
  - Georgia statewide survey, 20-23 December 1987 (Box 246)
  - Georgia statewide survey, 20-23 December 1987 (Box 246)
  - Pennsylvania presidential studies wave I, 20-28 August 1980 (Box 246)
  - Kentucky presidential tracking, 24 October 1980 (Box 246)
  - Michigan statewide track, 1980 (Box 247)
  - California statewide tax survey, undated (Box 247)
  - Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in the State of Maine, 13-14 November 1990 (Box 247)
  - California statewide voters, March 1982 (Box 247)
  - Republican National Convention, state summary book, February 1984 (Box 247)
  - South Carolina presidential tracking, October 1980 (Box 247)
  - Michigan presidential tracking, October 1980 (Box 247)
  - Ohio presidential tracking, October 1980 (Box 247)
  - West Virginia tracking, November 1984 (Box 247)
  - Mississippi/West Virginia tracking, November 1984 (Box 247)
  - Reagan transparencies, circa 1980 (3 folders) (Box 247)
  - NRA Elections projections, February and May 1978 (Box 247)
  - Internal Congressional Elections Projections (Prioritized by GOP Strength), 6 September 1978 (Box 247)
  - Presidential experiment reports, 1976 (Box 247)
  - Presidential experiment reports, 1976 (contd.) (Box 249)
  - Bush thermometer ratings, 20 July 1984 (Box 250)
  - Various election issues, 1984 (Box 250)
  - Attitudes on nuclear arms, 1984 (Box 250)
  - High frontier poll, 1984 (Box 250)
  - Opinions on the environment, 1984 (Box 250)
  - Blue collar, 1984 (Box 250)
  - Wisconsin bushfire aggregate results, 1984 (Box 250)
  - Iowa tracking aggregate results, 1984 (Box 248)
  - Labor (an issue), 1984 (Box 248)
  - Alitalia market study, 1987 (Box 248)
  - Party identification shifts, 1984 (Box 248)
  - Republican national convention analysis, 1984 (Box 248)
  - Phoenix values, October 1993 (Box 248)
  - Western European attitudes, April 1983 (Box 248)
  - NBC+ABC tape, 3 November 1980 (Box 248)
  - Truck values research, undated (Box 248)
  - Phoenix values, October 1993 (Box 248)